<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>hayami.blog</title>
    <link>https://hayami.blog/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on hayami.blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>na</language><atom:link href="https://hayami.blog/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>zoome founded</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/zoome/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2019 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/zoome/</guid>
      <description>Today, I established zoome LLC. Pronunciation of zoome is same as zoom.
https://zoome.co.jp/ Develop and management services mainly AR / VR.
Meaning of company name When you hear the zoom, you will think of quickness. and also airplane climb and camera zoom.
I thought that this might also mean &amp;ldquo;growth&amp;rdquo;. It is an image that plants grow up and become huge.
If tail er to zoom, at least in Japan there is the name of the bike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gyoen in 2018</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/2018-gyoen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Dec 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/2018-gyoen/</guid>
      <description>  I go to Shinjuku Gyoen several times each year. It&amp;rsquo;s a place where I can enjoy the change of seasons, something that can be difficult to experience in urban areas.
The cherry blossoms in spring, the prairies of summer, and the maple leaves during autumn each have their own charm. However, in January, I was able to view a world of white—a snowscape—when snow was falling heavily.
                                                                                                      </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Apple Shinjuku Store in Tokyo</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/apple-store-shinjuku/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/apple-store-shinjuku/</guid>
      <description>Today, Apple Store Shinjuku is opened.
High five parade It was 9:45 when I arrived at the storefront. It was 15 minutes before opening time, but I was just on time for the start of the staff&amp;rsquo;s high five parade.
From within the store, people wearing Apple staff t-shirts came trailing out in one line. They called out &amp;ldquo;Yay!&amp;rdquo; to the people who had been watching the situation inside the store while reaching out their hands for high fives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A succulent plant and Japanese style bonkei exhibition</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/2018-bonsai-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/2018-bonsai-1/</guid>
      <description>I participated in the ”An exhibition and sale of succulent plant design works and Japanese style tray landscapes” hosted by The &amp;ldquo;I Love Plants club&amp;rdquo; I joined.
At the entrance there was a cherry-blossom bonsai.
  Students&#39; work Nakamura&amp;rsquo;s work.
        Kimura&amp;rsquo;s work.
    Okamoto&amp;rsquo;s work.
      Siotsu&amp;rsquo;s work.
  Hattori&amp;rsquo;s work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>α7R III Review: Sony&#39;s best 8K camera</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/a7r3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Jan 2018 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/a7r3/</guid>
      <description>I purchased Sony&amp;rsquo;s α7R III.
Mostly I have only used a smartphone camera. However, when I held this Mirrorless, my field of vision expanded as if I had new eyes.
例えば新宿御苑へ行くと、普段なら見過ごす様な木のうねり、光の当たる所、影になる所が気になる様になった。風景をどう切り取れば美しい写真になるか考える癖がついた。
The photographs in this article use α7R III and SEL2470GM for those not described.
In addition, EXIF is left in the original 8K photo.
Overwhelming resolution α7R III と聞くとまず思い浮かぶのは解像度だろう。8Kの最高画質は凄まじい。
以下の微妙な写真をご覧頂きたい。
  8K photo
この写真から切り出して、仮にInstagramに等倍で投稿するとこうなる。
  この様に、小さくても画面内に写ってさえいれば、用途次第では素材として使えてしまう。</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A look back at 2017</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/2017/</guid>
      <description>I categorized ideas and clear my mind, throughout last year.
Books  Abundance: The Future Is Better Than You Think / Peter H. Diamandis &amp;amp; Steven Kotler Bold: How to Go Big, Create Wealth and Impact the World / Peter H. Diamandis &amp;amp; Steven Kotler The first six book of Rich Dad series / Robert T. Kiyosaki The Shift: The Future of Work Is Already Here / Lynda Gratton 人口から読む日本の歴史 / Hiroshi Kito Symphony No 9 / Yusuke Nakagawa Trump Revealed: An American Journey of Ambition, Ego, Money, and Power / Michael Kranish, Marc Fisher Return From Space / Takashi Tachibana Leadership and Self-Deception: Getting Out of the Box / The Arbinger Institute 決断力 / Yoshiharu Habu Love Theory / Keiya Mizuno  Classics  Gustav Mahler / Symphonie Nr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make kokedama</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/kokedama/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/kokedama/</guid>
      <description>I participated in the bonsai and bonkei (tray landscape) classroom held in Tokyo.
Since it was my first time, I learned how to make kokedama (bonsai) that are relatively easy to make and are easy to take care of.
Preparation Peat   Damp, sticky soil.
Sphagnum moss   White moss.
Necessary to improve water retention the peat.
Hypnum plumaeforme   Necessary to cover the peat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Restaurant &amp; Dessert in Kyoto</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/2017-kyoto/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/2017-kyoto/</guid>
      <description>Baikoudo (梅香堂)   IL PAPPALARDO     　This menu is &amp;ldquo;じっくり煮込んだ丹波篠山産 イノシシと上賀茂 高橋農園さんの有機堀川ゴボウのラグー 手打ちフェットチーネ&amp;rdquo;.
 Open: 11:30 am - 3:00 pm, and 6:00 pm - 10:00 pm
Close: Tuesday
IL PAPPALARDO, Myohoin Maekawacho 451-1, Higashiyama-ku, Kyoto Prefecture 605-0932, Japan
MARUMO BAKERY (マルモベーカリー)    Open: 7:00 am - 7:00 pm
マルモベーカリー, Fukakusa Nishiuracho 4-chome 51-1, Fushimi-ku, Kyoto Prefecture 612-0029, Japan
% ARABICA Kyoto Higashiyama (アラビカ京都 東山)    Open: 8:00 am - 6:00 pm</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A look back at 2016</title>
      <link>https://hayami.blog/en/2016/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hayami.blog/en/2016/</guid>
      <description>I had many encounters with entertainment in 2016.
Musics  Frederic WANIMA KANA-BOON Aimer ASA-CHANG &amp;amp; Junray Tama Motoharu Sano Yutaka Ozaki Kyu Sakamoto  Yutaka Ozaki is wonderful. His lyrics latch onto the hearts of junior and high school students.
I was especially moved by &amp;ldquo;Sotsugyo (Graduation)&amp;rdquo;. He sings about both the clear and the vague feelings of confinement that students feel from their teachers and society, and after instilling feelings of empathy, he says, &amp;ldquo;that all ends once you graduate.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
